Haseena Baig



haseena.baig118@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/haseena-baig-3a1651202



https://docs.google.com/document/ d/1YR Z8SDs5NXJ31o4NPFo 20F6yciD7L/edit

Summary

Content writing is not just about writing words; it's about choosing the right words. I'm an anxious and passionate team player with diversified skills and content writing experience. However, an investment in authentic learning is a better safeguard for a bright future.

I am an MSc (Animal sciences) graduate from Karakorum International University. I have real-time experience as a content writer. My specialization as a content writer includes Web Content, Blog writing, Ghostwriting, Copywriting, Social media content creation, and Technical writing.

I'm looking forward to talking with you.

https://bento.me/haseenawrites https://twitter.com/BaigHaseena

https://medium.com/@haseena-baig118

Experience



Content writer expert and Digital Marketer

Upwork

Dec 2021 - Present (1 year 11 months)

https://www.upwork.com/freelancers/~011be6f69b45e48acc

Content Writer

Fiverr

Aug 2022 - Present (1 year 3 months)

https://www.fiverr.com/haseenawrites?up_rollout=true

∩o Content Writer

Northnine

Oct 2021 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Working with research team of WASEP project collaborations with AKAH,AKU London and KIU.

KIU

Aug 2021 - Present (2 years 3 months)

https://medium.com/@haseena.baig118

Google

Aug 2020 - Present (3 years 3 months)

Working with HVRA and Climate change research team GBDMA.

GBDMA

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021 (5 months)

Education

Karakurum International University

Masters, zoology Jan 2019 - Apr 2021

Fatima jinnah college gilgit

Zoology and Botany Aug 2016 - Sep 2018

Licenses & Certifications

- Content and Copywriter American Continuing Education & Mentorship Academy https://acem.co/
- Digital marketing revolution University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign Coursera corsera.com
- Introduction to Google SEO Coursera
 9EHX8YNYZNFR
- The strategy of Content Marketing Coursera
 9EHX8YNYZNFR
- The Social Media Landscape Coursera
 UYY3QS4JXU8Z
- Meta Social Media Marketing Professional Certificate Coursera

Skills

Social Media Management • Social Media • Social Media Marketing • Facebook Ads • Instagram Marketing • Blog Writing · Article Writing · Content Writing · On-Page SEO · Keyword Research • Digital Marketing • Article Writing • Blog Creation • Microsoft Excel